Dennis Gonor

Software Engineer

San Jose, CA 95134 | +1 (510) 585-30-88 | dennis.gonor@gmail.com | Creen Card | github.com/honoyr | linkedin.com/in/gonor

C/C++, Java, JavaScript (ES6), TypeScript, Angular, Axios, Node.js, Express, API design knowledge, SQL, MongoDB, HTML, CSS, Webpack, npm, Linux, Unix, bash, Git Flow, Google Cloud Platform, Design patterns, OOP, Jira, Agile/Scrum

Summary

2+ years of commercial experience in building scalable web services and applications. I build flexible scalable and testable software applying my experience from my previous projects. I am always following the best practices in coding style, have experience with CD/CI integration and UNIT/INTEGRITY testing.

Experience

POSTOHUB: April 2019 - present (Fremont, CA)

Software Engineer, Co-founder

PostoHub is an email marketing tool to send millions of emails.

Responsibilities:

- Monitored and managed the PostoHub email ecosystem to ensure that PostoHub can continue to attract and retain enterprise customers.
- Optimized processes, tools, and data to ensure that customers get the full value of the PostoHub platform.
- Our team became a finalist for the Global Startup Architecture hosted by AWS. I initiated and support to take part in the challenge.
- Received 15k \$ from Amazon Portfolio Program (AWS Activate).

I have an in-depth understanding of the technical aspects of email, including FBLs, DKIM, SPF, DMARC. I have knowledge in email deliverability and requirements from a legislative (CANSPAM, CASL, GDPR etc.) and ISP (Gmail, Microsoft, Yahoo! etc.) perspective.

- Designed and implemented Email Editor user retention grew by 33%.
- Implemented integration and administered 3rd-party email deliverability tools.
- Developed/maintained and extended PostoHub frontend and backend website and app.
- Looked for and proposed changes to the code base and processes that improve the quality and efficiency of the product such as:
 - registration process bounce rate decreased by 68%.
 - uploading user data decreased from 10 to 3 sec.

Tools and Technologies: AWS, Node.js, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Angular, Git

Founder and Executive Producer

- Searched for new clients
- Designed and implemented a corporate website
- Adopted CRM system, created company's internal Wikipedia
- Arranged and managed every single aspect of movie production (budgeting, logistics, scouting for locations, hiring and managing staff, renting equipment etc)

Achievements: Our movies were successfully sold to the biggest video content distributors. One of them is present on Amazon Prime Video. A few of our short movies got festival awards including RiFF best international film production award.

AQUACLEAN: 2009 - 2017

Business Owner

Ran aquarium service company and online pet store with 16 000 items.

Technical Experience

Colorizer B&W Photo Colorization Web Application - I created this project with my friend to

be able to colorize old black & white family pictures.

Open Source 42 School Student Portal - open source project on github

Lingua Voice application for English learners created for the Bixby Marketplace

Education

42 Silicon Valley 2017 -2020

Software engineering school in the San Francisco Bay Area - Computer Science.

KYIV NATIONAL ECONOMIC UNIVERSITY 2008 - 2013

Master Degree, **Finance**.

Skills & Interests

- Language: Fluent Russian and Ukrainian
- Hobbies: Aquariums, Robotics, IoT, building my Family Tree. I love travelling!

*Online resume - site.cab